Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Stereographic Cards
2.1.8
Marist College
  Box 1604
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Looking N. over Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument and the Heart of Indianapolis, Ind., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Monument Circle, Indianapolis, Ind.: When in 1924, Indianapolis became the capital of the new state of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Moving Sand Dunes which Bury Forests, S. Shore of Lake Michigan, Ind., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sand Dunes on the Shores of Lake Michigan, Indiana: Presence of sand dunes is usually accompanied by barrenness, lack of water, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2-verso (Box 1604)
  - Harvesting Celery Blanched by Boards in Michigan's Famous Celery Fields, Kalamazoo, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Harvesting Celery Near Kalamazoo, Michigan: The region about Kalamazoo has made a reputation for itself in the production of celery, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3-verso (Box 1604)
  - Mammoth Building Housing Administrative Offices of General Motors, Detroit, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Mammoth Office Building of General Motors, Detroit, Mich.: Detroit is the automobile manufacturing center of the world., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4-verso (Box 1604)
  - Pouring Off Cylinder Blocks in the Ford Plant, Detroit, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Pouring Off Cylinder Blocks, Ford Plant, Detroit, Michigan: Each one of the hundreds parts of a motor vehicle must go through many processes, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5-verso (Box 1604)
  - Motor-testing Room in an Automobile Plant, Detroit, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Testing The Motor, Automobile Manufacture, Detroit, Michigan: In this room of a Detroit automobile factory the motors are tested, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6-verso (Box 1604)
  - Packing Salt into Barrel for Shipment, St. Clair, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Packing Salt In Barrels, St. Clair, Mich.: Find St. Clair on the map of Michigan? Which way is it from Detroit? From Grand Rapids? From Cleveland?, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7-verso (Box 1604)
  - Large Iron Ore Boat Coming Into Sabin Locks, Sault Ste. Marie, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Large Iron Ore Boat Coming Into Sabin Locks, Sault Ste. Marie, Michigan: The Great Lakes furnish the most remarkable inland waterway, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8-verso (Box 1604)
  - Pouring Molten Copper into Ingot Molds. Calumet-Hecla Smelters, Lake Linden, Mich., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Pouring Copper Into Molds. Calumet, Mich.: Copper-bearing rock is blasted free from the lode, or mother vein, and then dumped into tram cars., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9-verso (Box 1604)
  - Chicago's Skyline and Lake Shore Drive, Looking N. from Entrance of Field Museum in Grant Park, Illinois., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Chicago's Skyline and Lake Shore Drive: From a struggling frontier town in 1830, Chicago has developed into one of the most rapidly growing, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Lindbergh Beacon and Palmolive Building at Night, Chicago, Illinois., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Most Powerful Light Ever Produced By Man: From the top of the 65-foot steel tower surmounting the Palmolive Building, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11-verso (Box 1604)
  - Michigan Avenue, North from Straus Tower, Chicago, Ill., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Michigan Avenue, North from Straus Tower, Chicago, Ill.: The magnificent array of great buildings extending for more than a mile, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12-verso (Box 1604)
  - In the Heart of the Shopping District on State Street, Chicago, Ill., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Heart of the Shopping District, State Streetm Chicago: In every great city, some one street seems destined to become world famous, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13-verso (Box 1604)
  - Great Union Stock Yards, Largest Live Stock Market on Earth, Chicago, Ill., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Great Union Stock-Yards, Chicago, Ill.: Chicago is the greatest live-stock market and meat packing center in the world., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14-verso (Box 1604)
  - Ford Trimotor Cabin Plane Leaving Chicago with Passengers and Mail for Minneapolis, Minn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Ford Trimotor Cabin Plane Leaving Cicero Airport, Chicago, for the Twin Cities: The giant airplae before us, just warming up her motors, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15-verso (Box 1604)
  - Shearing Sheep with Power Driven Shears, Kirkland, Ill., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Shearing Sheep with Power-Driven Shears, Kirkland, Ill.: Here is another development of modern industry. In pioneer days our sheep, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16-verso (Box 1604)
  - Harvesting and Loading Silage Corn in Wisconsin's Famous Dairy Region., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Harvesting and Loading Silage Corn, Wisconsin: The dairy farm presents peculiar problems. The soil must be made to produce those foods, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17-verso (Box 1604)
  - Leaping Chasm Between Cliffs Sculptured by Prehistoric Streams, Dalles of the Wisconsin River., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Dalles of the Wisconsin River: We are in the southwestern part of Wisconsin near Kilborn. The valley up which we are looking, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18-verso (Box 1604)
  - Sacking and Weighing Flour by Automatic Machinery, Minneapolis, Minn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sacking and Weighing Flour by Automatic Machinery, Minneapolis, Minn.: The spout shown on the right in the picture is of smooth, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19-verso (Box 1604)
  - "Where the Falls of Minnehaha, Laugh and Leap into the Valley," - Minneapolis, Minn., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: "Where the Falls of Minnehaha Laugh and Leap into the Valley": The rivers and lakes of Minnesota form about one-twentieth of the state's area., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20-verso (Box 1604)
  - Muscular "Lumber Jacks" Hewing Out Trees in the Forests of Northern Minnesota., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Hewing Timbers by Hand in the Minnesota Pineries: These muscular men, squaring up a big log by the use of hand axes alone, so that, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21-verso (Box 1604)
  - Digging Potatoes by Hand and by Machine, Red River Valley, Minnesota., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Old and the New Way of Digging Potatoes, the Red River Valley, Minn.: The potato crop is one of the most important crops of our country., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22-verso (Box 1604)
  - Gigantic Piece of Engineering - Power Dam Locks in the Mississippi River between Keokuk, Iowa and Hamilton, Ill., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Power Dam and Locks in Mississippi River at Keokuk, Iowa: This wonderful structure of power-dam and locks which had been talked of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23-verso (Box 1604)
  - Shropsire, Oxford and Cotswlod Sheep in Pasture, Iowa State College, Ames., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Three Breeds of Sheep, Iowa: This picture was taken on the farm of the Iowa State Agricultural College at Ames, the leading institution, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24-verso (Box 1604)
  - Natural Pyramids in the Bad Lands, West of Dickinson, N. Dakota., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: In the Heart of the Bad Lands, Near Dickinson, N. Dak.: It was into the midst of this desolate region of strange natural formations and, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25-verso (Box 1604)
  - State Game Lodge, Custer State Park, Black Hills, South Dakota., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: State Game Lodge, Custer State Park, Black Hills, S. Dak.: In recent years, since the automobile jas beem steadily increasing the volume, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26-verso (Box 1604)
  - Plowing Rich Prarie Soil with Tractor, South Dakota., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Plowing Prarie Soil With Tractor, S. Dak.: Modern farm machinery has reached its greatest development in our Middle Western and Western, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27-verso (Box 1604)
  - Overlooking Sugar Beet Fields and Refinery from Scott's Bluff, Platte River Valley, Nebraska., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sugar-Beet Fields and Refinery From Scotts Bluff, Platte River Valley, Nebraska: Beet sugar first came into commerical importance when, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28-verso (Box 1604)
  - Unloading Sugar Beets from Wagons and Railway Cars at the Sugar Factory, Nebr., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Unloading Sugar Beets from Wagons and Railway Cars at the Sugar Factory, Nebraska: In this view a farmer has just driven in from a near by, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29-verso (Box 1604)
  - Mounted Sioux Indians in "Full Feather" Leaving Camp, Nebr., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sioux Indians in Full Feather, Nebraska: Do you remember "The Peace Pipe" in Longfellow's The Song of Hiawatha? Here are a few lines, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30-verso (Box 1604)
  - Magnificent Ten-Million-Dollar Eads Bridge over the Mississippi at St. Louis, Mo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Magnificent Eads Bridge Over Mississippi at St. Louis: The Eads Bridge spans the Mississppi River and connects St. Louis. Missouri with, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31-verso (Box 1604)
  - Shaft House, Smelter and Tailing Pile, Zinc and Lead Mines, Joplin, Mo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Shaft House, Smelter and Tailing Pile, Zinc and Lead Mines, Joplin, Mo.: Joplin, Missouri, is the center of zinc and lead production in the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32-verso (Box 1604)
  - Poland China Hogs Feeding in a Rich Alfalfa Pasture, Kansas., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Poland China Hogs in an Alfalfa Pasture, Kansas: Hogs are extensively raised in the corn belt. Corn and hogs are linked in most farmers', circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33-verso (Box 1604)
  - Hereford Cattle in Kansas Feeding Pens, Showing Open Air Feeding Shed, Manhattan, Kan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Feeding Hereford Cattle, Manhattan, Kansas: This is a fine herd of Herefords. They are all thoroughbreds that are bing made ready for market., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34-verso (Box 1604)
  - Primary Assembling of Planes in an Airplane Factory at Wichita, Kansas., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Assembling Fusilages of Airplanes in a Wichita, Kansas factory: The rapid development of aviation in less than three decades has been, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35-verso (Box 1604)
  - A Forest of Derricks in the Burkburnett Oil Fields, Texas., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Burkburnett Oil Field, Texas: The oil fields of our country all look very much like this one in northern Texas. In the tall derricks which, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36-verso (Box 1604)
  - Cotton Gin, Greenville, Texas, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Cotton Gin, Greenville, Texas: This view shows you the improved machine that has made possible the extensive growing off cotton., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37-verso (Box 1604)
  - General View of Alamo Plaza, Famous Alamo Mission at the Right, San Antonio, Texas., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Alamo Plaza and Mission, San Antonio, Texas: San Antonio is the largest city in Texas, having a population of approximately 200,000., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38-verso (Box 1604)
  - Pueblos of the Taos Indians, Taos, N. Mexico., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Pueblo of Taos Indians: The Pueblo Indians of the Southwest were very different from those farther east and north. They were partly, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39-verso (Box 1604)
  - Indian Women Baking Bread, New Mexico., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Laguna Indian Women Removing Bread from Primitive Oven, New Mexico: In every part of North America the primitive Indians possessed, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40-verso (Box 1604)
  - Reclaiming Vast Areas by Irrigation-Great Roosevelt Dam, near Phoenix, Ariz., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Great Roosevelt Dam near Phoenix, Arizona: The Roosevelt Dam is built across Salt River, Arizona, and is part of the system irrigating, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41-verso (Box 1604)
  - Where the Desert Has Been Made to Blossom like a Rose-Salt River Valley, Arizona., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Salt River Valley, Arizona: Within a comparatively few years vast stretches of land in the southwestern United States have been transformed, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42-verso (Box 1604)
  - Grand Canyon from El Tovar Hotel, Arizona., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Across the Canyon from El Tovar: A stupendous spectacle lies spread before us, for sublime majestic splendor without an equal in all the world., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43-verso (Box 1604)
  - South from Cape Royal to Precipice Point, and the Big Bend in the Colorado River, Grand Canyon Nat. Park., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Grand Canyon from Cape Royal on the North Rim: We are looking southeast, Coconino Plateau extends eastward from the view opposite., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44-verso (Box 1604)
  - "Dismantled Towers and Turrets Broken"-Cliff Palace in the Mesa Verde, Colorado., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Cliff Palace in the Mesa Verde, Colorado: Mesa Verde National Park is in the southwest corner of Colorado. The word mesa means table., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45-verso (Box 1604)
  - Ute Indian and Family, Colorado, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Ute Indian and Family, Colorado: We find much that is worthy of study in the scene before us. First to attract attention, perhaps, is the Indian man, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46-verso (Box 1604)
  - Peering Down into Awesome Depths of Box Canyon, Ouray, Colorado., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Box Canyon, Ouray, Colorado: Ouray, the "Gem of the Rockies," is 389 miles by rail from Denver, in western Colorado. Box Canyon, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47-verso (Box 1604)
  - Stamp Mill and Gold Concentrator, Ouray, Colorado., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Stamp Mill and Gold Concentrator, Ouray, Colorado: Gold is sometimes found free, but more often it is combined with other metals., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48-verso (Box 1604)
  - The World's Highest Bridge Spanning the Royal Gorge, near Canon City, Colo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Famous Royal Gorge Suspension Bridge: Stretching like a silver cobweb, this beautiful suspension bridge carries the unique, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49-verso (Box 1604)
  - Canyon Front of Union Pacific Lodge, North Rim of Grand Canyon of the Colorado, Arizona, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Canyon Front of Union Pacific Lodge, North Rim of Grand Canyon of the Colorado, Arizona: Covering the high plateau on the north of Grand Canyon, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50-verso (Box 1604)
  - In the Royal Gorge, Grand Canyon of the Arkansas, near Canton City, Colo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Royal Gorge, Arkansas River, Near Canyon, City Colo.: This railroad track belongs to the Denver and Rio Grande Railroad. Pike's Peak is, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51-verso (Box 1604)
  - Majestic Pike's Peak, through the Gateway of the Garden of the Gods, Colorado., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Pike's Peak, Through Gateway of Garden of the Gods, Colorado: You are looking nearly west. It is the road from Manitou two miles away, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52-verso (Box 1604)
  - Harvesting Barley-Combined Harvester and Threshing Machine Drawn by Tractor, near Fort Collins, Colo, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Havesting Barley with Combined Harvester and Threshing Machine Drawn by Tractor: This machine is a harvester and thresher that is, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Most Famous Sight in Yellowstone Park, "Old Faithful" Geyser in Action., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Most Famous Sight in Yellowstone Park-"Old Faithful" Geyser in Action: We are in the northwestern corner of the state of Wyoming, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54-verso (Box 1604)
  - Crater of New Geyser Which Burst Forth in 1928 in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: A New Wonder in the Land of Wonders-The Geyser of 1928, Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming: Travelers who have not been in Yellowstone, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55-verso (Box 1604)
  - Riverside Geyser Spouts Its 100-Foot Jet Obliquely across Firehole River, Yellowstone Nat. Park, Wyo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Riverside Geyser Sending Its 100-Foot Jet Obliquely Across Firehole River: If we are so fortunate as to be there at the right time, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56-verso (Box 1604)
  - A More Enchanting Wonder, Nature Never Knew-Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone, Yellowstone Nat. Park, Wyo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone, Yellowstone Nat. Park: You are looking about southwest from a projecting angle in the rim of the canyon, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Brimming Basins of Jupiter Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs, Yellowstone Nat. Park, Wyo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Brimming Basins of Jupiter Terrace, Mammoth Hot Springs: We are standing before one of the faces of wonderful Jupiter Terrace, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58-verso (Box 1604)
  - Great Herd of Elk Driven by Snows from the Mountains of Yellowstone Nat. Park. Wyo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: A Herd of Elk Driven By Snows from the Mountains of Yellowstone National Park, Wyo.: A few decades ago the American elk, or wapiti deer, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Shepherd and His Flock on a Ranch in Montana-Our Leading State in the Sheep Industry., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sheperd and Flock on Ranch in Montana: The eastern three-fifths of the state of Montana consists of rolling plains lying at an elevation, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60-verso (Box 1604)
  - Copper Smelters and Mines, Butte, Mont., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Copper Smelters and Mines, Butte, Montana: Butte (but) is the largest city in Montana. It has a population of about 40,000. It is located, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61-verso (Box 1604)
  - Mt. Grinnell and Mt. Gould, S.W. across McDermott Lake from Chalets. Glacier Nat. Park. Mont., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Mount Grinnell and Mount Gould, Across McDermott Lake, Glacier Nat. Park: Glacier National Park, the "Switzerland of America," is situated, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62-verso (Box 1604)
  - In the Village of Blackfeet Indians near St. Mary's Lake, Glacier National Park, Montana., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: In Village of Blackfeet Indians Near St. Mary's Lake, Glacier, Nat. Park, Mont.: The Blackfeet Indians are the westernmost of the Algonquin, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63-verso (Box 1604)
  - Chief Two-Guns-White-Calf and Companions in Medicine Lodge Ceremony, Glacier National Park, Mont., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Chief Two-Guns-White-Calf and Companions in Medicine Lodge Ceremony, Glacier National Park, Mont.: It should not be difficult to recognize, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64-verso (Box 1604)
  - Thousands of Head of Cattle on a Great Cattle Ranch near Boise, Idaho., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Great Herd of Cattle on an Idaho Ranch, near Boise: The huge herds of cattle which a few decades ago were pastured on the open ranges, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65-verso (Box 1604)
  - Salt Lake City, Utah-Looking North over Temple Square to the Capitol., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Salt Lake City, utah: The capital, the largest city, and a county seat is Salt Lake City's position in the state of Utah. The city has a population, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66-verso (Box 1604)
  - Sunset in the Silent City, Bryce Canyon, Utah., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sunse in Bryce Canyon: Bryce Canyon is probably the most astonishing blend of exquisite beauty and grotesque grandeur ever produced, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67-verso (Box 1604)
  - Cedar Breaks, Utah, from Point Perfection., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Cedar Breaks, Utah, from Point Perfection: Twenty-five miles due north of Zion Lodge on an air line is a series of vast amphitheathers, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Temple of Zion from the West Rim Trail, Utah., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Temple of Zion from the West Rim Trail, Utah: Now we have ascended to the West Rim Trail and are looking down into magnificent, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Bad Lands in Eastern Nevada., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Bad Lands in Eastern Nevada: Before us lies a stretch of territory that is fittingly named the Bad Lands. It is a portion of what is known as, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70-verso (Box 1604)
  - Main Business Street from the Bank of the Truckee River, Reno, Nevada., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Truckee River and Virginia Ave., Reno, Nevada: Nevada, the sixth largest state of the Union, has a scant 80,000 population. Its vast desert area and lack of rainfall have much of the state, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71-verso (Box 1604)
  - Mt. Tallac (9715 Ft.) from across Fallen Leaf Lake, California., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Mount Tallac Seen Across Fallen Leaf Lake, California: It has been only within recent years that many region of surpassing beauty and grandeur, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Sierras from Glacier Rock, Yosemite Valley, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: The Sierras, Yosemite Valley, California: The Sierra Nevada (si-er r ne-v d ) Mountains extend north and south through the entire length, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Glorious Yosemite Valley, from Glacier Point, California., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Yosemite Valley From Glacier Point, California: We are up near the eastern end of the valley, looking towards Nevada and Idaho and, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74-verso (Box 1604)
  - Majestic Yosemite Falls Beautifully Reflected in Nature's Mirror, Yosemite Valley, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Yosemite Falls, Highest in the World, California: The Yosemite National Park lies in the heart of the Sierra Nevada Mountains, 140 miles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75-verso (Box 1604)
  - Orange Blossoms and Mature Oranges Growing on the Same Tree, California, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Oranges and Orange Blossoms, California: Perhaps the best known of California's agricultural industries is the production of citrus fruits., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76-verso (Box 1604)
  - Majestic El Capitan, Calif. Rising Sheer 3,604 Feet and Twice as Great as Gibraltar, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77 (Box 1604)